

ROEE EIDAN

Full Stack and Mobile Developer

Portfolio Website: www.roeeeidan.com

LinkedIn Profile : www.linkedin.com/in/roee-eidan-23a2a7a6

SUMMARY

I'm a passionate software developer with 4 years of experience building web and mobile apps primarily using React, React Native, Node.js, and AWS. I'm an independent, self-driven, and motivated individual that loves to solve complex problems and to collaborate with others.

EXPERIENCE

Sandbox (Creative Agency)

Software Development Lead

May 2020 - Current

- Developed a social media app using React Native, GraphQL, MongoDB, and AWS
- Hired and directed the work of a junior developer
- Contributed to the ongoing product design

ROSS (SAS - AI Legal Research Tool)

Software Developer - Growth Team

Sep 2019 - April 2020

- Developed the option of multi-user firm subscription on the app, including payments and user permissions
- Developed the onboarding of a new user to the app
- Developed the case study pages on the marketing website
- Contributed to ensuring the 13 million law cases in our database are searchable
- Contributed to the integration with another app to transfer brief documents and analyze them

Digital Native (UX/UI Agency)

Software Developer - Independent contractor

Jan 2018 - April 2019

- Developed the company's new website
- Developed web pages for a leading fitness company
- Developed a new website for a law firm
- Developed a new website for a restaurant
- Developed a new website for a photographer

Good Weekend Co. (Trip Planning Tool)

Software Developer

Jan 2019 - June 2019

- Planned and executed the development of the app
- Contributed to the design of the app

Gruifrom (Digital Agency)

Team Lead

Dec 2017 - Aug 2019

- Led a team of 4 developers to develop a new front end for an oil stock trading platform in Asia using Vue.js
- Led the development of a new website for an Art school
- Led the development of a new website for a real estate development company

Locksmith Near Me

Website Designer and Developer

Oct 2017 - Dec 2017

• Designed and developed a website for a local locksmith company

SKILLS

- HTML/CSS/JS/Animations/DOM
- React.js, React Native, Redux, Vue.js, Angular
- Node.js, GraphQL, Express
- MongoDB, Postgress
- S3, Lambda, EC2, RDS, SES, Firebase
- Segment, Mixpanel
- Figma, Sketch, Lottie
- Wordpress, Webflow, Rise
- Machine Learning,
 Natural Language Processing

EDUCATION

Natural Language Processing Udacity 2020

Machine Learning

Coursera - Stanford University 2019

iOS Development Course

Brainstation 2017

Web Development Immersive

Brainstation 2016

MILITARY SERVICE

Israel Defence Force, K9 Unit

Combat Commander

July 2013 - July 2016

- Trained a team of 6 soldiers from an entry combat level to a K9 specialist
- Managed and oversaw the combat operations
- Completed performance reviews with combats

VOLUNTEER

llan Israel - disabilities children summer camp

Mentor, Guide, Friend

June 2009 - June 2013

Every summer I spent two weeks helping, and guiding a child with disabilities through his summer camp.

CONTACT

108 Montrose Ave. Toronto, ON

roee.eidan@gmail.com

(416) 834-9657